export interface ReadingText {
    id: number;
    question: string;
    answer: string;
    audio: string;
  }
  
  const Answershortquestion: ReadingText[] = [
    {
      id: 120,
      question: `If 'fact' is a real happening, what is an unreal event or unreal story?`,
      answer: `fiction`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324425/audios_tts/audio_1e40837d-5f90-4c70-8829-af8ac6a7696f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 119,
      question: `In which room of their home would someone usually wash their clothes?`,
      answer: `Laundry room`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324426/audios_tts/audio_bc1e1635-ecb9-4d69-bccf-6b00225e3477.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 118,
      question: `Which of these would probably be found in most homes around the world - a computer, a bed or a television?`,
      answer: `Bed`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324427/audios_tts/audio_78611814-de70-444c-893a-f1ce0a2f15dc.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 117,
      question: `In which century did the automobile become manufactured on a mass scale?`,
      answer: `The twentieth century`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324429/audios_tts/audio_3e960536-3a12-4cd7-8416-a04437e862cd.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 116,
      question: `Which day of the week starts with 'th'?`,
      answer: `Thursday`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324431/audios_tts/audio_69696985-a71b-489b-bc14-4d4293a63fad.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 115,
      question: `In which season would people be least likely to go snow skiing?`,
      answer: `Summer`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324432/audios_tts/audio_3a018335-43ef-4df2-8930-379842f9a761.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 114,
      question: `Would letter or email be the fastest way to get a message to your professor?`,
      answer: `Email`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324434/audios_tts/audio_ebda4ad3-bc4c-44b3-9e8e-ce8b777f6ec4.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 113,
      question: `Jane and Peter have three children. They are 4, 13 and 15 years old. They only have one son, who is their youngest child. How old is their middle child?`,
      answer: `13 years old`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324435/audios_tts/audio_0ae269c1-244f-494d-a717-6dd5fc51f33f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 112,
      question: `What can be added to a drink to cool it down on a hot day?`,
      answer: `Ice`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324436/audios_tts/audio_80e0f80b-f139-48ad-91b9-880bab6a950d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 111,
      question: `What kind of equipment is used to protect motorbike riders' brains from injury?`,
      answer: `Helmet`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324437/audios_tts/audio_5fc350c0-dc7e-481d-aa8f-e408025a08d7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 110,
      question: `What do we call the line between a sunset and the sea?`,
      answer: `Sea-sky-line / horizon`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324438/audios_tts/audio_ba31ca06-1272-4396-8058-cb17f16bf1d7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 109,
      question: `Cash usually includes banknotes and ?`,
      answer: `Coins`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324439/audios_tts/audio_cdc381cf-4fa8-4a31-bf0d-ed030c5acb47.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 108,
      question: `What do we call a place where airplanes land and take off?`,
      answer: `Airport / airfield / airdrome`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324440/audios_tts/audio_b88af87a-5d89-4e96-a46d-fd69ea194d3a.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 107,
      question: `Which of these is greater a billion or a trillion?`,
      answer: `A trillion`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324441/audios_tts/audio_01a24514-787b-4a5a-bbd7-c83a55b78d31.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 106,
      question: `If you don't feel like eating, what do we say you don't have?`,
      answer: `Appetite`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324442/audios_tts/audio_b7ee23fa-2aef-4d24-8649-f9370e29078d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 105,
      question: `What is the job title of a person who paints pictures for a living?`,
      answer: `Painter`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324443/audios_tts/audio_25408bb8-ff49-4213-9af8-32ee96cc1565.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 104,
      question: `Which building material comes from tree trunks?`,
      answer: `Wood`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324445/audios_tts/audio_f307f4d5-2e92-4a0b-b5e6-3ff4e73aa34c.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 103,
      question: `Which is the last month of the year?`,
      answer: `December`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324446/audios_tts/audio_41f664ac-4cf1-4fc4-b379-8c6b676a4c2d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 102,
      question: `Which is the organ cardiologists specialize in?`,
      answer: `Heart / hearts`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324447/audios_tts/audio_a70abfe1-1985-41a2-8016-866339821491.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 101,
      question: `Which is the longest: a decade, a millennium or a century?`,
      answer: `Millennium`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324448/audios_tts/audio_5f8d8518-89d6-4479-ab6f-a6da2ebbb4c2.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 100,
      question: `What is a list of historical events arranged in time order?`,
      answer: `Chronology / timeline`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324450/audios_tts/audio_91d96a58-36c7-456b-8827-b827724f15f6.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 99,
      question: `If a figure is hexagonal, how many sides does it have?`,
      answer: `Six`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324451/audios_tts/audio_f4d02820-f821-4f11-a117-c078ad057e6f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 98,
      question: `What do you call a person who does not give up?`,
      answer: `Persistent / perseverant`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324452/audios_tts/audio_15114809-d05b-48ec-ab5d-39af63e02a36.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 97,
      question: `Which is the most common symbol of a country at international gatherings?`,
      answer: `Flag`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324453/audios_tts/audio_cda1c049-7675-4e23-9f80-77863ada5486.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 96,
      question: `A compilation of songs or photos is also called what?`,
      answer: `Album`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324454/audios_tts/audio_3d0180ff-c5d6-4cbe-a45c-e3fe8f090007.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 95,
      question: `What do people cast in an election?`,
      answer: `Vote / ballot / suffrage / poll`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324455/audios_tts/audio_a3326057-7468-4499-912a-05000101a5fe.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 94,
      question: `What is the term used for a place or an institution where one can park extra funds to earn a return or borrow funds by making an extra payment?`,
      answer: `Bank`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324457/audios_tts/audio_acf8f146-a757-4e03-b14f-8105ca5de376.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 93,
      question: `Which device tells us time?`,
      answer: `Watch / clock`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324458/audios_tts/audio_dd0b8c29-5f73-419d-96a4-427bd632a336.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 92,
      question: `What is the term used for raised tall geographical structures that usually have cooler climate?`,
      answer: `Mountains / hills`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324460/audios_tts/audio_14b72e50-79c5-407d-958a-483850a1822c.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 91,
      question: `What is the term used for the principal male character opposite a hero in a movie or a story?`,
      answer: `Villain / Antagonist / devil / monster`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324462/audios_tts/audio_a53fd3a6-4876-4211-853c-6acee9a55b4a.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 90,
      question: `Something that can be eaten is edible. What is something that can be heard?`,
      answer: `Audible`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324463/audios_tts/audio_bfd54b98-4d31-4b3e-8cc4-058ce51a09bd.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 89,
      question: `What is the term used for the life history of a person written by himself?`,
      answer: `Autobiography / memoir`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324464/audios_tts/audio_ef9b58c7-40ff-4cc4-890c-84bdeaf3c7e1.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 88,
      question: `What would be the opposite of compulsory service?`,
      answer: `Voluntary service`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324466/audios_tts/audio_551003ea-7559-47d6-a935-7d847935a8d7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 87,
      question: `What is the term used for see-through items such as clear glass?`,
      answer: `Transparent / lucid / pellucid / crystal`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324467/audios_tts/audio_8fe5c0b4-5092-4167-8678-1b252c22bd7e.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 86,
      question: `If something that will die one day is mortal; what term will be used for something that never dies?`,
      answer: `Immortal`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324468/audios_tts/audio_5df3e767-2396-4d8f-97cd-9680d6de5021.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 85,
      question: `What is the name of ceremony in which two people get married?`,
      answer: `Wedding`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324471/audios_tts/audio_02819fd2-bb05-4b54-b043-15aa1c14b97f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 84,
      question: `Which item of cutlery has several prongs usually three?`,
      answer: `Fork`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324472/audios_tts/audio_6fb59fa2-7c6b-45fe-9d42-91864b94acb7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 83,
      question: `Who is more likely to have sleep problems caused by their work schedule an accountant, a university lecturer or an international pilot?`,
      answer: `International pilot`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324473/audios_tts/audio_76da3818-f65f-4ede-8eaa-f36e4d487848.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 82,
      question: `What piece of furniture is specifically designed for sleeping all through the night?`,
      answer: `Bed`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324475/audios_tts/audio_53ee8a20-808b-4848-9b22-768c875668cd.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 81,
      question: `Would most people spend greater amount of time eating, drinking or sleeping?`,
      answer: `Sleeping`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324477/audios_tts/audio_83b97a3f-fa7d-4ea0-accb-230fe33b9363.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 80,
      question: `In normal circumstances would four hours of sleep per night be too much, too little or just right for most people?`,
      answer: `Too little`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324478/audios_tts/audio_1153ffd8-fea0-46bf-8b80-688471d05be7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 79,
      question: `Which one word is used for a brother or sister?`,
      answer: `Sibling`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324479/audios_tts/audio_897fcb42-065d-4155-ac35-6ca2a94884ce.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 78,
      question: `Who is the main journalist responsible for producing a newspaper or magazine?`,
      answer: `Editor`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324480/audios_tts/audio_3daa66aa-2808-446f-b3cd-0ac22d25816f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 77,
      question: `What is the word in geometry for a shape that has three sides?`,
      answer: `Triangle`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324481/audios_tts/audio_b0dffe65-7c60-4df3-b77e-6ead6e2c301d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 76,
      question: `Where can people go to borrow books?`,
      answer: `Library / bibliotheca`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324482/audios_tts/audio_5705e102-1563-49c4-81a9-f7080f41e5b1.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 75,
      question: `Which sweet food is produced by bees?`,
      answer: `Honey`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324483/audios_tts/audio_8c725110-469c-4361-98f5-15a3d180630b.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 74,
      question: `When ice is at room temperature, what does it become?`,
      answer: `Water / liquid`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324484/audios_tts/audio_7499e18b-a018-4d31-8bc1-4ed582cc61ce.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 73,
      question: `What is the opposite of east?`,
      answer: `West`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324487/audios_tts/audio_d990000f-b083-4621-bb8d-184fefd850f5.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 72,
      question: `How many months are there in a year?`,
      answer: `Twelve`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324489/audios_tts/audio_08a28dc0-1182-4edd-9160-2f5705986f06.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 71,
      question: `What type of food is an apple?`,
      answer: `Fruit`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324490/audios_tts/audio_82152189-d857-4250-b79c-710552cd687f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 70,
      question: `What do people wear if they can't see very well?`,
      answer: `Glasses / contact lenses / spectacles`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324491/audios_tts/audio_1a991749-b593-4362-8438-1eb37e8a8ec4.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 69,
      question: `If something is not expensive, what do we say it is?`,
      answer: `Cheap / inexpensive`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324492/audios_tts/audio_f6e7bba6-5c86-4e9c-8159-1373e217e4b3.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 68,
      question: `What is a collective term for cows and bulls, especially on a farm?`,
      answer: `Cattle`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324493/audios_tts/audio_6a4ee3ba-4f3b-49ab-b305-feffb453c557.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 67,
      question: `What do we call the study of living things?`,
      answer: `Biology`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324494/audios_tts/audio_629c28de-9362-4f0c-ac52-d1da74f14ae5.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 66,
      question: `What do we call a book that contains lists of words with their meanings?`,
      answer: `Dictionary`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324494/audios_tts/audio_1c7d9213-fc05-4801-89d0-2cc813dcd100.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 65,
      question: `What do we call the organs in our chest that we use to breathe?`,
      answer: `Lungs / lung`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324496/audios_tts/audio_74a39048-76ef-4ab4-8ae3-fbc96163d6fb.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 64,
      question: `What word is used for someone who watches a sports event?`,
      answer: `Spectator`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324497/audios_tts/audio_374df0ec-c306-48c0-8b9c-ff3ff4ce9372.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 63,
      question: `What term is used for the amount of money you pay a landlord for living in his house or apartment?`,
      answer: `Rent / rental`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324497/audios_tts/audio_45f02238-1da1-4260-9a4d-4c46b50da7a7.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 62,
      question: `What is the job title of someone who designs buildings?`,
      answer: `Architect`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324498/audios_tts/audio_bbf5ee7c-50e0-4b66-ae59-9445b37c1d2a.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 61,
      question: `Where would you go to see exhibits of dinosaurs?`,
      answer: `Museum`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324500/audios_tts/audio_75dd3724-acab-40ba-bc13-f717b5ce9b67.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 60,
      question: `What is the common term for websites such as Facebook and Twitter?`,
      answer: `Social Media / social networking`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324501/audios_tts/audio_f17f1f75-9d83-4ee5-8194-016e22d2501d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 59,
      question: `If someone lives in an urban area, where do they live?`,
      answer: `City / town`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324502/audios_tts/audio_1c36f7c5-2d95-4319-943c-82a8109b3dac.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 58,
      question: `Ice sports are likely to feature in which Olympics - Summer or Winter?`,
      answer: `Winter`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324503/audios_tts/audio_dac20888-bb3a-4909-b713-df0a8ad423a4.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 57,
      question: `Which major branch of science deals with classification of living things?`,
      answer: `Biology`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324505/audios_tts/audio_fa533a0e-af95-4d3a-be67-1c70fb3e8846.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 56,
      question: `What’s the color of the medal that a champion gets?`,
      answer: `Golden / gold`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324507/audios_tts/audio_1c0492c4-2413-46fe-b8dc-dd8eb4a5b783.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 55,
      question: `To improve their health and fitness, most people either try to improve their diet or...?`,
      answer: `Do more physical exercise`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324508/audios_tts/audio_338e97d2-befb-4623-a8e8-8372c495f944.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 54,
      question: `At what age does someone become a teenager?`,
      answer: `Thirteen`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324509/audios_tts/audio_1711ea0f-a97d-41fa-9b74-e96dfd7c801e.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 53,
      question: `What desk should you go to when you first arrive to stay at a hotel?`,
      answer: `Reception / check-in / front desk`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324510/audios_tts/audio_36aee38d-904e-4f99-a6bc-ebbb26ad7a5d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 52,
      question: `If something such as fabric or medicine is artificially made, not natural, what do we say it is?`,
      answer: `Synthetic / artificial`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324511/audios_tts/audio_7c0eae6d-3ec1-494a-9f26-26f1f22aee38.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 51,
      question: `What do you call a professional trained to treat illnesses?`,
      answer: `Doctor / medicine`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324512/audios_tts/audio_4425baa3-6242-412b-8672-2618554d4ed8.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: `Would it be better to go jogging at noon or in the early morning if you want to avoid the hottest part of the day?`,
      answer: `In the early morning`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324513/audios_tts/audio_5910634a-300b-4bad-998a-6ceb08800a7a.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: `What do you call the alphabetical list at the end of a textbook that tells you where to find specific information?`,
      answer: `Index / Reference`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324514/audios_tts/audio_98dd5641-9a3a-4aed-bc3e-c4eddbd87ad3.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: `What do we call a company or organization that gives money to a sports or arts event in exchange for advertising?`,
      answer: `Sponsor / patron / supporter`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324516/audios_tts/audio_2b4f44e5-da21-45b7-a590-ebc2e35b9c37.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: `Which country is in the southern hemisphere, Australia or Canada?`,
      answer: `Australia`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324517/audios_tts/audio_652dc578-625c-4237-a75a-6f3986df995f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 46,
      question: `What do we call the meeting where an employer asks a potential employee question about their work experience?`,
      answer: `Interview`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324518/audios_tts/audio_9ba5cf3d-71bd-4afc-bda0-ea94c05288b1.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: `Which animal does wool come from?`,
      answer: `Sheep`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324519/audios_tts/audio_2384c54f-a644-4f13-8444-9ec9b8747f26.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: `What do things become when they come to a halt?`,
      answer: `Stationary / static / pause / quiescence`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324520/audios_tts/audio_1914ff9d-2124-4120-8d84-77b139fc6d2f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: `Which short TV program or a part of TV program tell whether it will be sunny or rainy tomorrow?`,
      answer: `Weather forecast / weather report`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324521/audios_tts/audio_95d04c74-d44a-4911-a395-6d7fc7e2fbaf.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: `What is the place at home where you cook food?`,
      answer: `Kitchen / cookhouse / cookroom`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324523/audios_tts/audio_8caefbcf-4a12-4468-a83f-83d2d10ceb3c.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: `What is the thing that contains steps and allows you to climb up indoor?`,
      answer: `Ladder / stairs / stair / ladders / staircase`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324524/audios_tts/audio_0476f28f-e783-451d-8893-b425544adb9b.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: `What's the name of the annoying sound that people sometimes make when they breathe while sleeping?`,
      answer: `Snoring / snore`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324525/audios_tts/audio_b5c91f76-2e61-49f5-8489-c521dfe154f1.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: `How do you call a student that has finished his first year?`,
      answer: `Sophomore`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324526/audios_tts/audio_45c51aef-1865-4969-ace5-f2da21dd49ae.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: `What do we call the first paragraph of a report?`,
      answer: `Introduction`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324527/audios_tts/audio_0f083b17-8f71-4bbd-a0f2-da0ff28e4145.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: `Which part of your leg can make it possible to bend?`,
      answer: `Knee`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324528/audios_tts/audio_96f36c7c-c2c9-48d9-bfed-665904afabbb.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: `What natural resource is used by a carpenter?`,
      answer: `Wood / timber`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324529/audios_tts/audio_b6aa0876-fb9c-4fe2-b361-e8fc8c579b35.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: `Which color do we make by blending black and white?`,
      answer: `Grey`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324530/audios_tts/audio_5c801d7a-6411-425e-a800-c3d2e7799512.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: `What is the opposite of artificial?`,
      answer: `Natural`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324531/audios_tts/audio_bddc62c8-9679-4bcd-8747-b1421c4f1fa2.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: `What is the opposite to ‘still’?`,
      answer: `Moving / active / dynamic`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324532/audios_tts/audio_b61929ed-5e61-495e-bf75-dadacdc2791c.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: `What device do you use to measure your weight?`,
      answer: `Scale / weighing machine`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324533/audios_tts/audio_47bec471-2e97-496e-9ba4-6442886d4707.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 31,
      question: `What do you use to test the body temperature?`,
      answer: `Thermometer`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324534/audios_tts/audio_e814429b-5aa1-4b85-87f7-3a96a9dc70ee.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: `What is the opposite of ending in a film or movie?`,
      answer: `Prologue`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324535/audios_tts/audio_383c2c45-5030-44c7-ad4d-7e7d6746e21f.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: `What is the room that is under the ground floor?`,
      answer: `Basement`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324536/audios_tts/audio_d0c2a11c-47d8-4b3a-8da9-2bf46b45d589.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 28,
      question: `What do we call people who write songs?`,
      answer: `Songwriter / composer`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324537/audios_tts/audio_0ba4003e-363c-42b3-9be0-67d141a6e210.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: `What subject involves the study of the Periodic Table?`,
      answer: `Chemistry`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324538/audios_tts/audio_a4f53ad7-a155-4e43-ae47-4a4f0a9d9cdf.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: `What do we call the sound when people clap their hands?`,
      answer: `Applause`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324539/audios_tts/audio_cd380e9d-6bf7-41d4-aa73-efcb7fc59b94.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: `How do you call someone with no hair?`,
      answer: `Bald`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324540/audios_tts/audio_53a744cb-36e4-4a79-9503-78647c038d8b.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: `What device is used to measure the height of mountains?`,
      answer: `Altimeter`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324541/audios_tts/audio_4b6f717a-b829-497a-a55b-348c021d4d71.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: `Which one in the four seasons has the lowest temperature?`,
      answer: `Winter`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324543/audios_tts/audio_af4504ea-32b3-46e8-a205-68faaf990b7c.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: `Which day of the week starts with 'th'?`,
      answer: `Thursday`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324544/audios_tts/audio_c06511ab-1857-4dd1-932f-77783f121c60.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: `What do we call the subject that studies weather and temperature?`,
      answer: `Meteorology / climatology`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324545/audios_tts/audio_4a2aa9b4-5c9d-41e3-b32a-929a3e4f0fa0.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: `What does 'subterranean' mean?`,
      answer: `Underground`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324546/audios_tts/audio_c8a5424e-3b28-4cd6-ace0-0c580c32367d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: `What is the act of reusing waste materials?`,
      answer: `Recycling`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324547/audios_tts/audio_48b6ffa6-0e6a-4c5a-a721-3ce00bc69cff.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: `What do we use to launch a space shuttle?`,
      answer: `Rocket / booster`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324548/audios_tts/audio_10728368-2ad5-460d-bc1c-5ea5ae6d0bba.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: `What do we call a period of 1000 years?`,
      answer: `Millennium`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324549/audios_tts/audio_02277b45-6e87-4449-ae40-52923a14a96a.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: `What is the study of religion called?`,
      answer: `Theology`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324550/audios_tts/audio_fdc2ab21-0bcd-4406-a182-25a4f39e4e8b.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: `What is the second month of the year?`,
      answer: `February`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324551/audios_tts/audio_807a02fd-a037-4e81-837c-943ae5524596.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: `What is the opposite of majority?`,
      answer: `Minority`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324553/audios_tts/audio_85827a3d-578a-4c82-aae9-09e8bf5cd52d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: `What is the main building of a large company or an organization?`,
      answer: `Headquarters`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324554/audios_tts/audio_a5fd01a5-3b73-4fad-aa94-8a03e18d04f3.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: `What do we call a person who pays rent to the landlord?`,
      answer: `Lessee / tenant`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324555/audios_tts/audio_c8611c25-3a43-427c-b4d9-571fedadd055.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: `What do we call a set of answers to exercises or problems?`,
      answer: `Key`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324556/audios_tts/audio_e2526c6f-9218-4290-90ba-2b2f49f3510d.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `What is 'BA' for, such as history and literature?`,
      answer: `Bachelor of arts`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324557/audios_tts/audio_379370fb-0a2c-485f-83d1-8e8ac67f0a19.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `What do we describe the space with no air in it?`,
      answer: `Vacuum`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324558/audios_tts/audio_70bb403e-a359-48e8-863e-795e2a277e8e.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `What is the opposite of 'guilty'?`,
      answer: `Innocent`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324559/audios_tts/audio_6a8aa1e9-1746-4904-8911-b81030528738.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `What is another way to say the arrangement of musical notes in a tune?`,
      answer: `Melody`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324560/audios_tts/audio_050afc30-4d34-4985-b06c-e5398a9c8420.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `What is the connecting part between two bones?`,
      answer: `Joint`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324561/audios_tts/audio_a17a2662-6912-48af-a079-3a1362d73e6b.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `What do we call a large container used for storing oil?`,
      answer: `Drum / barrel`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324562/audios_tts/audio_5377e195-01c9-4034-ba89-25b57df1b598.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `What do we call the female's partner in a marital relation？`,
      answer: `Husband`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324563/audios_tts/audio_76d517ec-f4f5-40d9-b07c-327fcede3c85.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `What instrument is used to measure angles in geometry?`,
      answer: `Protractor`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324564/audios_tts/audio_e7cebed2-376e-4790-8cf2-1b6a66b71bb2.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What do we call the state of sharing the same opinion?`,
      answer: `Agreement`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324565/audios_tts/audio_00ae5bf2-f36f-4357-ba92-950dbf9e3991.mp3`
    },
    {
      id: 1,
      question: `What do we call a set of answers to exercises or problems?`,
      answer: `Key`,
      audio: `https://res.cloudinary.com/ddy824awb/video/upload/v1763324566/audios_tts/audio_59a61844-2518-48fc-a4b8-a5659954d7c3.mp3`
    },
  ];
  
  export default Answershortquestion;
  